modworkshop.net 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which modworkshop.net collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [modworkshop.net](http://modworkshop.net/), [pd2stash.com](http://pd2stash.com/) and [pd2stats.com](http://pd2stats.com/) websites ("sites"). This privacy policy applies to the sites and all products and services offered by modworkshop. 

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our sites, register on the sites, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our sites. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our sites anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain sites related activities. 

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our sites. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our sites, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

Web browser cookies

Our sites may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the sites may not function properly. 

How we use collected information

modworkshop.net may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve our sites_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other sites feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our sites. 

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other websites, including websites which have a link to our sites, is subject to that websites's own terms and policies. 

Third party apps

pd2stats.com and modworkshop.net provides a service that allows developers to create Applications (each, an "App") that can access data that we have collected about you and your uploads. Once authorized those Apps will be able to request the information from our API. modworkshop.net does not control the use and storage of your data by those Apps. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies which state the use of your data. 

Advertising

Ads appearing on our sites may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Google Analytics

pd2stats.com and modworkshop.net uses Google Analytics to track user behaviour on our websites. This data is anonymous and will only be used to further improve our webservices. 

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other websites, including websites which have a link to our sites, is subject to that websites's own terms and policies. 

Changes to this privacy policy

modworkshop.net has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this sites, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://pd2stats.com/terms.php). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the sites following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this sites, or your dealings with this sites, please contact us at: [tatsuto@live.de](mailto:tatsuto@live.de?Subject=PrivacyPolicy)  

Latest Changes

This document was last updated on September 27th, 2017
